Contact

Jl.kpt rahmad budin gg.cempaka No.30 , Lk.08 0813-7915-2174 (Mobile) muhammad01111999@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/muhammadhikam (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Microsoft Excel
User Interface Design
JavaScript

Languages

english (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Menjadi Google Cloud Engineer Google Cloud Computing Foundations

Cloud Practitioner Essentials (Belajar Dasar AWS Cloud)

Belajar Dasar Pemrograman JavaScript

MUHAMMAD HIKAM

Cloud Computing student at Bangkit academy 2023 || Ungraduated Informatics in University Muhammadiyah Sumatera Utara || Freelancer

Medan, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Summary

About Me

As a student at Muhammadiyah University, North Sumatra, I have experienced quite a long journey. I am also active in various activities on campus, such as being active in UKM and others. I am currently running a revive program in semester 6 lectures and have high enthusiasm for programming. I have experienced long journey and dedication in developing skills and knowledge in rising learning path cloud computing, I also actively participate in various projects and tasks that are being raised, such as the final mobile development project .During the program's revival, I have interacted a lot with fellow students who have the same interests, formed study groups to complete projects, and supported one another. I can also take advantage of the resources provided by the awaken academy where the learning paths really help me to improve my skills in programming, to share knowledge and expand my network. I usually participate in a community whose environment has been provided by the awaken academy, In the community, I am very enthusiastic about developing analytical skills and solving problems. I learn to analyze problems, plan solutions, and implement effective programming code. When faced with difficulties, I did not give up, but continued to look for solutions to problems and tried various approaches, starting from reading the resources provided by the awaken academy and consulting a mentor, My enthusiasm for programming also drives me to stay up to date with the latest developments in the IT industry, i follow the news, read blogs or articles, and take online courses besides at rise academy on relevant topics. I may also participate in programming competitions or opensource projects to improve my skills and increase my visibility in the programming community and then

Overall, as an enthusiastic program-running student and passionate about programming, I have demonstrated a strong commitment to

self-development and attaining high levels of expertise in this field. With my passion and dedication, I can definitely achieve my goal of becoming a skilled and successful programmer in the future.

Experience

Telkom Indonesia Student Intern March 2023 - Present (1 year 1 month) Medan Kota, North Sumatra, Indonesia

PT Charoen Pokphand Ind. Tbk Production Operator November 2019 - Present (4 years 5 months) Medan Kota, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Education

Universitas Muhammadiyah Sumatera Utara (2020 - 2024)

SMAN 3 MEDAN · (2015 - 2018)